wildflowercases.com 2017-02-22

# Privacy Policy – Wildflower Cases

**Privacy Policy  **

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the http://www.wildflowercases.com and Wildflower Cases and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Wildflower Cases include http://www.wildflowercases.com and Wildflower. The Wildflower website is a ecommerce site. By using the Wildflower website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**  

Wildflower may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Wildflower's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Wildflower. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Wildflower website.  Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Wildflower's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.  As you browse wildflowercases.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with wildflowercases.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit this page (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising. Wildflower encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Wildflower so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Wildflower is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Wildflower website.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Wildflower collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.  Wildflower may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Wildflower and its affiliates. Wildflower may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. Wildflower does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Wildflower may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Wildflower, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. Wildflower may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Wildflower, in order to determine what Wildflower services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Wildflower to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. Wildflower will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Wildflower or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Wildflower; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Wildflower, or the public.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Wildflower secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Children Under Thirteen**

Wildflower does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Wildflower by contacting us here: 

\- Web page: http://www.wildflowercases.com/pages/contact-us

\- Email: wildflowercases [at] gmail.com

\- Phone: 323-552-9722

**Changes to this Statement  **

Wildflower will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Wildflower encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Wildflower is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  

Wildflower welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Wildflower has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Wildflower at:  Wildflower Cases 5042 Wilshire Blvd #21094 Los Angeles, CA 90036 Email Address: wildflowercases [at] gmail.com Telephone number: 323-552-9722 Effective as of April 18, 2012.
